Adam M Soukup

adam.soukup@ymail.com / adamsoukup.com

Graphic and Interactive Multimedia Designer

Hard working graphic designer with years of experience producing creative content in a fast paced environment. Ability to manage multiple projects, using various types of design software and technology. I produce original material for specific company needs with a proven track record of meeting tight deadlines, while keeping company costs down. Received excellence awards for going above and beyond normal tasks within given timeframes and work schedule.

Core Competencies

Photoshop
Illustrator
In-Design
After Effects
Articulate Studio
Adobe Captivate
HTML5 / CSS3
Gulp

Professional Experience

Freelance Designer 2015 – Present

Web Design, E-Learning, Graphic Design

CME Group 2009 – 2015

The Worlds Leading Derivatives Marketplace

Creative Services Specialist

Created Graphic, Video and Interactive Design to Increase Public Interest

- Collaborated with different departments and managers to produce educational material
- Designed official 30sec company video spot for use in London rugby stadium
- Created interactive demos and training videos for internal and external use, used to explain products offered through CME Group and new features of trading technology software
- Recorded and edited voice overs for podcasts, online videos, and interactive demos
- Made animated gifs (web banners and event announcements) for internal and external sites
- Provided technical support while hosting live webinars and meetings
- Submitted performance management plan to division leaders quarterly detailing completed projects and future goals, while finding ways to improve productivity and brand standards

Tech Systems 2004 – 2009

Design Consulting Agency Assisting CME Group

Online Content Consultant

Created Graphic and Web Design Projects for emegroup.com

- Created and updated web pages to aid in new look and feel of the site
- Helped redesign website twice to comply with merger of new partners and new branding
- Produced interactive charts and graphs that showed company growth and projections
- Designed Flash animations (banners) and demos
- Created static imagery and banners using Photoshop
- Provided technical support and hosted live webinars and meetings

Education

Bachelor of Fine Arts, American Academy of Art Chicago, 1998 - 2002